qualitystockphotos.com 2014-06-13

# Qualitystockphotos.com - Privacy Policy

Effective Date: 08/15/2011  
This privacy statement describes how Kozzi Inc. (“Kozzi”) collects and uses the personal information you provide on our Web site: [www.qualitystockphotos.com](http://www.qualitystockphotos.com/). It also describes the choices available to you regarding our use of your personal information and how you can access and update this information.  
We will share your personal information with third parties only in the ways that are described in this privacy statement.  We do not sell your personal information to third parties.     
Kozzi Inc. has been awarded TRUSTe's Privacy Seal signifying that this privacy policy and practices have been reviewed by TRUSTe for compliance with TRUSTe's program requirements including transparency, accountability and choice regarding the collection and use of your personal information.  TRUSTe's mission, as an independent third party, is to accelerate online trust among consumers and organizations globally through its leading privacy trustmark and innovative trust solutions. If you have questions or complaints regarding our privacy policy or practices, please contact us at [privacy@qualitystockphotos.com](mailto:privacy@qualitystockphotos.com)

We collect the following personal information from you

  * Contact Information such as name, email address and Unique Identifiers such as user name and password
  * Preferences Information such as product marketing preferences.

**Uses of Information**

Kozzi Inc. is committed to protecting your privacy. The information collected by Kozzi Inc. is solely used to manage and maintain our website in order to create a more satisfactory experience for our users.

Use of your personal information is collected by Kozzi Inc. to:

  * create and manage your account;
  * provide customer service;
  * perform research and analysis aimed at improving our products, services and technologies;
  * to display content that is designed for your interests and preferences;
  * to run contests, select entrants, and choose prize winners;
  * to run our interactive areas;
  * to keep you up to date on the companies activities through communications such as bi-weekly newsletters, information about new products and services being introduced to the website.  
_Please keep in mind if you exempt yourself from such marketing communications you will continue to receive bi-weekly newsletters and product and service updates. If you wish to no longer receive newsletters or marketing communications you may follow the unsubscribe instructions contained in the emails you receive_.

Personal information collected by Kozzi Inc. may be stored and processed in Canada or any other country in which Kozzi Inc. or its parent, affiliates, subsidiaries or agents maintain facilities, and by providing us with your personal information and using our sites or services, you consent to any such transfer of information outside of your country. If you would like to exercise any of your personal information protection rights (which includes your right to have personal information deleted from our databases), please contact [privacy@qualitystockphotos.com](mailto:privacy@qualitystockphotos.com).

When you visit this site, certain types of non-personal information, such as the website that referred you to us, your IP address, browser type and language used, and access times, can be automatically collected as part of the site’s ability to shift to consumer needs and activity.   

**Tell-A-Friend**

If you choose to use our referral service to tell a friend about our site, we will ask you for your friend’s name and email address.  We will automatically send your friend a one-time email inviting him or her to visit the site. Kozzi stores this information for the sole purpose of sending this one-time email and tracking the success of our referral program.

Your friend may contact us at [privacy@qualitystockphotos.com](mailto:privacy@qualitystockphotos.com) to request that we remove this information from our database.

**Legal Disclaimer  
**We may disclose your personal information

  * as required by law, such as to comply with a subpoena, or similar legal process
  * when we believe in good faith that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, protect your safety or the safety of others, investigate fraud, or respond to a government request,
  * to any other third party with your prior consent to do so.
  * if Kozzi is involved in a merger, acquisition, or sale of all or a portion of its assets,  you will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on our Web site of any change in ownership or uses of your personal information, as well as any choices you may have regarding your personal information.

**Access to Personal Information  
**If your personally identifiable information changes, or if you no longer desire our service, you may correct, update, delete/deactivate it by making the change on our member information page or by emailing our Customer Support at [support@qualitystockphotos.com](mailto:support@qualitystockphotos.com)

We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

**Security  
**The security of your personal information is important to us.  We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it.  No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however.  Therefore, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. If you have any questions about security on our Web site, you can contact us at [support@qualitystockphotos.com](mailto:support@qualitystockphotos.com).

**Tracking Technologies**

_Cookies_

A cookie is a small text file that is stored on a user’s computer for record-keeping purposes. We use cookies on this site. We do/do not link the information we store in cookies to any personally identifiable information you submit while on our site.

Cookies offer users many conveniences when browsing our website. We use both session ID cookies and/or persistent cookies.  We use session cookies to make it easier for you to navigate our site. A session ID cookie expires when you close your browser. A persistent cookie remains on your hard drive for an extended period of time. You can remove persistent cookies by following directions provided in your Internet browser’s “help” file.

Persistent cookies are used to retain certain personal preferences that users may have. For example the background colour of the website can be changed, thus whatever colour the user chooses, this setting will be saved for the next visit. We also set a persistent cookie to store your passwords, so you don’t have to enter it more than once.  Persistent cookies can also enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our site.

The use of cookies by our service providers is not covered by our privacy statement.  We do not have access or control over these cookies. 

If you reject cookies, you may still use our site, but your ability to use some areas of our site may be limited.

_Log Files_

As is true of most Web sites, we use a third party tracking-utility partner to gather certain information automatically and store it in log files.  This information includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and clickstream data. 

We use this information, which does not identify individual users, to analyze trends, to administer the site, to track users’ movements around the site and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. 

**Links to Other Web Sites   **  
Our Site includes links to other web sites whose privacy practices may differ from those of Kozzi. If you submit personal information to any of those sites, your information is governed by their privacy statements. We encourage you to carefully read the privacy statement of any web site you visit.

**Notification of Privacy Statement Changes**  
We may update this privacy statement to reflect changes to our information practices. If we make any material changes we will notify you by email (sent to the e-mail address specified in your account) or by means of a notice on this Site prior to the change becoming effective. We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on our privacy practices.

**Children  
**Kozzi Inc. is a family friendly website, thus children are generally welcome to browse our website without parental consent. We cannot fully guarantee a child or parent will not be offended by our content but the content we upload is vetted. If you need any more information please contact [info@qualitystockphotos.com](mailto:info@qualitystockphotos.com)

**Contact Us  
**If you have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us at: [privacy@kozzicom](mailto:privacy@kozzicom) or via postal mail at:  
400 Matheson Blvd. East,   
Mississagua, Ontario, Canada   
L4Z 1P1
